Krishnakumar R. Yadav () Featured

Software Development, Application Programming, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, C#. Net, ADO. Net, Web API, ASP. Net MVC, jQuery, SQL Server, JavaScript, SDLC, AJAX



Current Designation: Manager -Software Developer Total Experience: 11 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Motilal Oswal Finvest Limited Notice Period: Currently Serving Notice Period

Current Location: Mumbai Highest Degree: MS/M.Sc(Science) [Computers]

Pref. Location: Mumbai

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: Banking/Financial Services/Broking

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Application Programming, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, Solution Architecture, C#. Net, ADO. Net, Web

API,ASP.Net MVC,jQuery,SQL Server,JavaScript,SDLC,AJAX,Software Development

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

A competent professional offering nearly 11 years of experience in designing & developing Applications/Software using Microsoft Technologies C#.Net, ASP.Net, ADO.Net, Web API, ASP.Net MVC, jQuery, SQL Server and JavaScript

Rich experience in managing complete Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC) including requirement analysis, development, coding, design, enhancements, customization, UAT, and other testing following Agile Methodologies for applications/products

Implementations & custom application solutions using ASP.NET, C# and .NET Framework

Extensive experience in designing User Interface using jQuery, AJAX as well as working on writing Stored Procedures in SQL Server-2012/2014

Rich experience in working on project with insightful knowledge of Object Oriented Programming (OOPs) using C# entailing analysis, design, development, and configuration management

Work Experience

Motilal Oswal Finvest Limited as Manager -Software Developer Nov 2016 to Till Date

Apr'20 - Present Motilal Oswal Finvest Limited as Manager

Aug'18 - Mar'20 Motilal Oswal Financial Services Limited as Assistant Manager

Nov'16 - Aug'18 Motilal Oswal Securities Limited Prabhadevi, Mumbai as Assistant Manager

Client: Motilal Oswal Financial Services Limited

Team Size: 2

Technologies: Asp.Net 4.5, C#, JavaScript, Query, Web API

Database: Microsoft SQL Server 2016

Client: Motilal Oswal Financial Services Limited

Team Siz: 5

Technologies: Asp.Net 4.5, C#, JavaScript, Query, Web API

C-Edge Technologies Ltd. as Assistant Systems Analyst Oct 2013 to Nov 2016

Softlink Global Pvt. Ltd as Software Engineer Feb 2011 to Sep 2013

planet electronics pvt ltd as Software Developer Sep 2009 to Sep 2010

software developer

Education

UG: B.Sc (Maths) from Mumbai University in 2007

PG: MS/M.Sc(Science) (Computers) from Mumbai University in 2009

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
C#.Net, ASP.Net, ADO.Net, Web API	
Asp.Net MVC, Jquery	
SQL Server, JavaScript	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

Affirmative Action

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

Employment Status: Full time

Work Authorization